KESY APRIANSYAH

+6283869052776 | kesyaprianysah@gmail.com| kesyapriansyah.vercel.app | https://www.linkedin.com/in/kesyapriansyah-12205721b/

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

Informatics Engineering students are experienced in information systems services, skilled at analyzing information systems, conducting business analysis, managing user questions and complaints, designing UI/UX, developing web and mobile applications, interacting with servers via API, and having high learning abilities.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Informatics engineering, Muhammadiyah Purwokerto University (2

(2021 - present)

• GPA 3.68

WORKING EXPERIENCES

CV. Bangkit Edukasi Indonesia (cobaupgradediri) – Purwokerto, Indonesia Co-Founder (April 2020 – present)

- **Developing a learning platform:** designing and developing an online learning platform that allows users to learn soft skills and hard skills. Ensure the platform is easy to use and effective for achieving learning objectives.
- Create a webinar landing page for product promotion.
- **Managing IT infrastructure:** maintaining the IT infrastructure of websites and learning platforms. Ensure that websites and platforms run smoothly and safely.
- **Monitor website performance:** Track and analyze website data to measure performance and identify areas for improvement.
- Analyze problems and create solutions in the form of products
- Seek funding: Seek funding to support growth and development

MSIB Mobile Development (Android) learning path: Bangkit Academy, Indonesia

- understand well the basic concepts of programming languages, programming functional, and object-oriented programming (OOP) using Kotlin.
- skilled in building Android applications that display lists and data details.
- Proficient in applying basic OOP concepts and their relationships to complete problems in software design using the 5 SOLID principles.
- Proficient in building applications that enable data retrieval from the Web API and store data locally.
- can build applications by implementing various existing components, such as UI, Animation, Localization, Background Process, Media, Sensors, Locations, Databases
- capable enough to start the final stage of the task, namely developing applications/solutions
 that validate product development skills and increasing the portfolio, namely the street
 vendor detection application.
- thoroughly understand Life Path, Growth Mindset, Power of Feedback, Time Management, Critical Thinking, Problem Solving, Adaptability, Resilience, Project Management, Professional Communication, Networking, Digital Branding

Universitas Muhammadiyah Purwokerto - Purwokerto, Indonesia

• Laboratory Asisstant (January 2020 - March 2020)

ORGANIZATIONAL EXPERIENCES

- Member of Research and Technology Department Informatics Engineering Student Association – Muhammadiyah Purwokerto University
 - Assigned to conduct research on problems that exist in the Informatics Engineering Study Program both from students and lecturers and even agencies and Help optimize and develop both new and existing technology in the Informatics Engineering Study Program, Muhammadiyah University, Purwokerto.
- person in charge of Informatics Engineering Study Club Informatich Enginering Muhammadiyah Purwokerto University
 - make a study roadmap and be responsible for all study club activities in informatics engineering at the University of

- Coordinator of the 2023 Informatics Engineering General Discussion Event
 - Lead the committee team in planning, preparing, and implementing the 2023 general discussion, Ensure the smooth running of the event and the achievement of the expected goals.
- Coordinator of the 2023 Informatics Engineering New Student Friendship Event
 Leading the committee team in planning, preparing, and implementing the 2023 Informatics
 Engineering event, including:Event concept and theme for the intimate evening, Preparing
 event proposals and budgets, Coordinating with various related parties, such as the
 committee, speakers, and vendors, Leading and motivating the committee team in
 completing tasks and responsibilities, Managing event logistics and accommodation,
 Ensuring the smoothness and success of the event.
- informatics creativity and competition 2023 event coordinator

 Leading the committee team in planning, preparing and implementing ICC 2023, guiding the course of the event, including opening, closing and announcement of winners. Ensure the smooth running of the event and the achievement of the expected goals.

PROJECT EXPERIENCES

- Creating Garena Free Fire clone website using React JS and Tailwind CSS
- Creating Kyt Helm clone website using React JS and Tailwind CSS
- Creating portfolio website with html css and js
- · Creating futsal field booking website using php
- Creating the appearance of the lemona bread application using react native
- Create a website and try upgrading your LMS using WordPress.
- Creating UI/UX JajanJalan application using Figma
- Create a social media GitHub Android application using the GitHub API.
- Create an Android application Story App.
- · create notes android application
- Create a live-tracking Android application for street vendors.

Certification training and awards

Bangkit, specializing in Mobile Developer	Bangkit Academy pdf
 Training on Creating Android Apps with Jetpack Compose 	Dicoding pdf
Training: Intermediate Android Application Development	Dicoding pdf
Android Application Fundamentals Training	Dicoding pdf
 Android App Learning Training for Beginners 	Dicoding pdf
Training to Learn Git with GitHub	Dicoding pdf
Basic Web Programming Training	Dicoding pdf
Fullstack Programming Training	Udemy <u>pdf</u>
 Embracing a Growth Mindset as a Software Engineer 	Indosat Ooredoo
Hutchison Digital Camp pdf	
 Learning Project Management Training 	Dicoding pdf
 Structured Query Language (SQL) Basic Learning Training 	Dicoding pdf
Baparekraf Developer Day 2023	Ministry of Tourism
and Creative Economy of the Republic of Indonesia pdf	
SOLID Programming Principles training	Dicoding pdf
 short class Software Engineering introduction to Frontend 	MySkill <u>pdf</u>
IT Talk "Get To Know Product Management In Tech Industry"	Paragon <u>pdf</u>
 Webinar Niagahoster LiteBites 66.0: Cyber Security 	Niagahoster <u>pdf</u>
 industrial work practice as a laboratory assistant 	Universitas
Muhammadiyah Purwokerto pdf	
 training Learning DevOps Fundamentals 	Dicoding pdf
Starting Basic Programming to Become a Software Developer	Dicoding pdf

SKILLS

Soft Skills: Communication, Teamwork, Leadership, Problem solving, Critical thinking, Adaptability, Project Management

Hard Skills: Kotlin For Android Development, React JS, HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP, Next JS, Boostrap, Tailwind CSS, UI UX Design, WordPress